“创始吸血鬼”前情提要
KLAUS: Previously on The Originals ;
这座城市曾经是我的家
我要夺回来
This town was my home once.
I want it back.
这城市已习惯了有国王的统治
The city grew accustomed
to having a king.
既然你想要这个宝座
You wanted this throne.
如果你不愿意做的话，那我来
If you won't do anything, I will.
基兰是我唯一的亲人
我受够了总是一个人
Kieran's the only family I have left.
I'm tired of being alone.
你本来是个收获祭女孩
但或许你不属于这里
You're supposed to be a Harvest girl,
but maybe you don't belong here.
战争一触即发，小提
A battle is brewing, T.
大家都忙着选择阵营
While everyone's busy choosing sides,
我会想办法夺回我们的城市
I'm gonna find a way
to take back our city.
日光戒指保护吸血鬼不受阳光侵害
KLAUS: Daylight rings shield
vampires from the sun,
那为什么不能有一个月光戒指
保护狼人免受诅咒之苦呢？
so why not a moonlight ring to
protect werewolves from the curse?
你和克劳斯米卡森做了交易？
You made a deal with Klaus Mikaelson?
我们最终可以控制自己
We could finally control what we are.
猎杀我们的人类
诅咒我们的女巫
The humans who hunt us,
the witches who curse us,
憎恨我们的吸血鬼
the vampires who hate us,
我们将不再只与他们势均力敌
我们将统治他们
we wouldn't just be their equals.
We'd be their superiors.
你起得真早
You're up early.
激情了一夜，我以为你会多睡会呢
After the night we had,
I expected you to sleep in.
是啊，但清晨的阳光是最佳的作画光源
Yes, well, morning sun
offers the best light.
别动
Hold still.
我快完成了
I'm almost finished.
如果在前世，这么赤裸着躺在这里
一定让我害羞死了
In my last life, I was far too
modest if I was in the nude.
那你可真是进步不少
Well, then consider
yourself much improved.
害羞是弱者才有的表现
Modesty is for the weak.
- 你不给我看看吗？
- 这幅画是一份礼物
-Well, are you gonna show me?
-The painting is a gift.
一份庆祝我们结盟的贺礼
A token to honor our pact.
我们的结盟？
昨晚如此美妙
Our pact?
We had such a lovely night
却只是你为达目的而使的手段
and now I see it was
all a means to an end.
一个能达到双赢目的的美好手段
A rather delicious means
to a mutually beneficial end.
告诉我，除了昨晚的欢愉
Tell me.
Beyond the pleasures of last night
和你承诺送给我的杰作
and the promise of what
I'm sure is an exquisite painting,
与你结盟对法语区的女巫们来说
what exactly would
a French Quarter witch gain
还有什么好处？
from aligning with you?
我亲爱的哥哥与城市里
Well, the treaty my
dear brother negotiated
各方势力所签下的协定
between the warring
factions of this city,
就是你亲自签名的那份
the one that you yourself signed.
尽管大家都有心遵守
但毕竟这里…
No doubt everyone means well,
but this is after all--
仍然是法语区？
-Still the French Quarter?
-(CHUCKLES)
一个充满着宿敌的城市
A borough rife with natural enemies.
你和你的女巫们需要的
What you and your witches need
是只有我能提供给你们的保护
is the protection only I can provide.
没有人，无论是吸血鬼还是狼人
No one.... not vampires,
not werewolves,
有我站在你们这边
就算是我哥哥也不敢招惹你们
not even my brother will dare trifle
with you if I am on your side.
作为交换…
And in exchange...
你要我给你什么呢？
...I am to offer you what, exactly?
我只希望你保证对我效忠
All I ask is for the promise
of your allegiance.
能有一个强大的女巫盟友总是有备无患
One never knows when a powerful
witch might come in handy.
我同意
Well, then.
莫妮克，你还好吗？
Monique, are you OK?
莫妮克，你听起来像是被附身了
Monique, you sounded like
you were possessed.
我没有被附身
I wasn't possessed.
我是在跟祖先们交流
I was channeling the ancestors.
他们说是时候完成收割仪式了
They say it's time
to complete the reaping.
为此，第四个收获祭女孩必须复活
To do that, the fourth Harvest
girl must be resurrected,
也就是说，洁妮薇必须死
which means...
it's time for Genevieve to die.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）
剧名：极度不安
我真是受够这些噪音了
Enough with all the racket!
有什么问题吗，弟弟？
主演：约瑟夫摩根
Is there a problem, brother?
各位，先离开好吗？
Gentlemen, please.
我只同意让你简单装修一下
主演：丹尼尔吉利斯
I agreed to a general sprucing up,
不是让你在这搭个马戏团
主演：丹尼尔吉利斯
not a bloody three ring circus.
不是让你在这搭个马戏团
大半个世纪来，马赛尔和他的手下
主演：菲比托金
Marcel and his minions
abused our home
对我们的家肆意践踏
主演：菲比托金
for the better part of a century.
或许你愿意住在这种废墟里，但我可不
主演：查尔斯麦可戴维斯
Now, you might be content
to live in squalor. I'm not.
我同意你哥哥说的
I agree with your brother.
法语区已进入了新时代
主演：莉雅派普斯
It's a new era in the French Quarter.
这地方也该好好翻新一下了
主演：丹妮儿坎贝尔
This place could use a makeover.
小心点，以利亚
主演：丹妮儿坎贝尔
Careful, Elijah.
当这女人同意你的说法时
说明她必有所图
When this one agrees with you, it's
a sure sign she wants something.
事实上…
我的确有个请求
Actually....
I do have a request.
我听说自从马赛尔限制女巫使用魔法后
I'm told our coven hasn't been
able to celebrate feast days
我们的族人便无法公开庆祝节日
in the open since Marcel
restricted the use of magic.
如今和平时代来了
我希望能有所改变
Now with the new peace,
I'd like that to change.
我想你已经决定一个特定的节日了
Am I to assume that you have
a certain feast day in mind?
恩典节
The Fete des Benedictions.
也就是祈福的节日
Feast of the blessings.
在过去，社区里的人们
向女巫们进献礼物
In the past, members of the community
offered witches gifts
以换取她们的祝福
in exchange for blessings.
我们想借这个机会
We'd like to use it as a forum
向公众介绍那些年轻的收获祭女孩
for introducing our young
Harvest girls to society.
你的族人试图破坏我的家庭
So your coven attempted
to destroy my family
而你让我的手足
承受了难以言喻的痛苦
and you yourself held my
siblings in unspeakable torment.
如今你居然请求让女巫开派对
And you would like
a party for the witches.
制片：克里斯多福贺利尔
(KLAUS LAUGHS)
我与你弟弟已冰释前嫌
I made my amends with your brother.
你何不好好考虑一下？
Why don't you think it over?
别这么不近人情，以利亚
Don't be such a stiff, Elijah.
游客们最喜欢热闹的节日了
The tourists love a good festival.
再说，还有什么比得上
Besides, what better way
to cement solidarity
向旧时敌人示好更有利于…
制片：兰斯安德森
than a show of faith
…巩固我们的结盟呢？
toward a onetime enemy?
一个你已走得过于接近的旧时敌人
A onetime enemy with whom you've
grown rather nauseatingly intimate.
谁说结盟的同时不能找点乐子呢？
Who said maintaining
alliances can't be fun?
你不是有些更应该做的事吗
One would think you'd
be a little more interested
比如说，关心你孩子的母亲？
in attending to the needs
of the mother of your child.
原来如此贴心的整修
都是为了她吧
So she's the reason behind this
oh-so-thoughtful renovation.
事实上，以利亚
我孩子的母亲在狼人中有很高的地位
Elijah, the truth is the mother
of my child is werewolf royalty.
她在河口与族人待在一起
She's far safer in
the bayou with her pack
比在我们身边要安全得多
than she would ever be here with us.
别担心，我会在她分娩前把她带回来的
Don't worry. I'll bring her
home before the birth.
我的孩子绝不会…
制片：邦妮怀斯
No child of mine
…在沼泽地里出生
will be born in a swamp.
开什么玩笑
说真的，这是怎么回事？
You've gotta be kidding me.
Seriously, what is going on?
这些人是谁？
Who are all these people?
为什么他们都如此怪异地站在那里？
Why are they standing out
here all weird and lurky?
他们来自各地的各个族群
They've come from all over.
All the packs.
为什么？
来看一个还没出生的婴儿吗？
Why? To see a baby
that isn't even born yet?
别提婴儿了
Forget the baby.
这些怪胎，他们是来看你的
These freaks,
they came here to see you.
要知道，因为你父母
You know, given
the place your parents
在族群中的地位，他们或许认为
held in pack hierarchy,
maybe they think
你就是他们等待多年的
编剧：玛格丽特麦金泰尔
you're gonna be the long-lost
狼人救世主什么的
编剧：麦可鲁梭
werewolf messiah or something.
太好了，还真是一点都没压力
导演：莱斯利里布曼
Great. No pressure or anything.
喂？
Hello?
奥利佛，关于我们谈的事
我相信你有进展了吧
Oliver. I trust you have an update
on the matter we discussed.
嗯…关于那件事
Yeah... About that.
如今这里聚集了无数狼人
We got wolves coming in
by the truckload right now,
要在这里面找一个人可不太客易
so it's gonna be a little
tricky to find just one guy.
毕竟你只给了我一个名字
I mean, all you gave me
was a first name.
没错，他叫凯瑞
Yes. His name is Cary.
金色头发、褐色瞳孔
He's got blond hair and brown eyes.
他是我的族人之一
来自东北大西洋族群的
He's one of my clan,
a distant relative
远房亲戚
from the Northeast Atlantic pack.
你若想继续我们的计划就得找到他
His presence is required if
we are to continue with our plan.
找到他，把他带来给我
You find him and you bring him to me.
好吧，我尽力
All right, fine. I'm on it.
还有一件事，我哥哥最近会邀请你
Another thing....
my brother will soon invite you
参加一场向女巫致敬的聚会
to a feast honoring the witches.
你和你的朋友们要识趣地接受邀请
You and your friends will
graciously accept the invitation.
凭什么啊？
Why the hell would I do that?
因为让以利亚觉得他的协定奏效了
Because if Elijah believes
his treaty is working,
他就不会来找我麻烦了
he'll be less inclined
to get in my way.
（卢梭酒吧）
你来干嘛？
What do you want?
我最近结识了一个友人
或许能帮你叔叔
I formed an alliance with someone
who may be able to help your uncle.
我猜是那个
别有用心的红发高个儿女吧
Let me guess.
Tall, redhead, axe to grind?
当初就是那些复活的女巫
Those resurrected witches
对基兰下咒的
are the ones who
hexed Kieran in the first place.
她又怎么会帮忙？
Why would she want to help?
因为我要她这么做
Because it's my decree that she does.
我想你至少说句“谢谢”吧
I believe the words you're
looking for are "thank you."
不管怎么说，你也可以拒绝
By all means,
say no if you have an alternative.
我拒绝
No.
等一下
Wait.
尽你所能帮助他
Do whatever you have to do.
Just help him.
你要我盯着克劳斯，我照做了
You wanted me to
keep an eye on Klaus. I did.
要我说，这是一件好事
If you ask me, this is a good thing.
他在讨好和你很要好的女孩
Him fawning all over a girl
这对我们很有利
you've got wrapped around
your finger helps us.
我不能让卡蜜受到伤害
I don't want Cami getting hurt.
女巫已经盯上她了
She's already got witches
spying on her.
你知道要是克劳斯发现我们俩是一伙的
Do you have any idea
what Klaus is gonna do
他会怎么做吗？
when he finds out that we hooked up?
不关我的事
Not my problem.
我们要担心的是那混合种在谋划什么
The thing we need to worry about
is what his hybrid ass is up to.
他和女巫们结成了一伙
He's got something going
on with the witches,
背着以利亚暗中谋划
and he's doing it
behind Elijah's back.
不管他居心何在，要是让我抓到把柄…
Whatever he's up to,
if I can find proof--
你要怎样？
跟他哥哥告状吗？
You'll what? You're gonna rat
him out to his older brother?
让他们兄弟反目成仇吗？
You're gonna turn them
against each other?
你已经被驱逐出法语区了
You're exiled from the Quarter.
你还没走近，以利亚就会要了你的命
Elijah even smells you
coming and you're dead.
我比你了解他们
You don't know them like I do.
他们已经互有戒心了
They're half turned
against each other already.
一千年的家族恩怨
自大、愧疚、嫉妒
A thousand years of family
drama, pride, guilt, envy,
全堆积成了一个炸药桶
all built up like a powder keg.
只需要你去把它点燃
All you have to do is light a match.
怎样才能点燃？
Then where do we buy matches?
醒醒吧，马赛尔，我们一无所有
Look around, Marcel.
We have nothing.
我起初也一无所有
I started with nothing.
直到我转变了你，一切才有起色
Hell, things didn't get
rolling until I turned you.
你和你的音乐，还有属于我们的城市
You and your music
and the whole city for the taking.
那些风光的日子，小提
Those were the days, T.
让我们把它夺回来
Let's go get 'em back.
谁让你做主的？
And who put you in charge?
我和祖先们交谈过了
I communed with the ancestors.
他们说是时候该让你做出牺牲了
They said it's time for
you to sacrifice yourself.
当然
Of course.
为我们族人履行我的义务是我的荣幸
It will be an honor
to fulfill my duty to our coven.
但现在时候未到
But it's not quite my time yet.
祖先们很清楚
The ancestors were very clear.
只有你死了，我们的族群才能
We need for you to die
so our community can have
获得收获祭的所有力量
the full power of the Harvest.
注意措辞，莫妮克
Careful, Monique.
不久之前，我也是祖先之一
Not so long ago,
I was one of those ancestors.
我就这样看着女巫一点一点地
A spirit forced to watch
as little by little,
向吸血鬼屈服
witches surrendered
everything to vampires.
我们或许已不受马赛尔控制
We may no longer live
under Marcel's thumb,
但我也不会乖乖服从于以利亚
but I for one don't particularly
enjoy answering to Elijah, either.
在我离开之前，我要确保
Before I take my leave,
I'd like to ensure
你们有能力掌控自己的命运
that you have the power
to control your own fate.
米卡森家的母亲艾丝塔是个强大的女巫
The Mikaelsons' mother,
Esther, was a powerful witch.
她的魔法书里有我们用得上的地方
Her spellbook contains enchantments
that we can use to our own ends.
我可以为我们族人偷来这本书
I can steal it for our coven
这样我们就再也不会受到欺压了
and we'll never be held
in subjugation again.
你们会得到需要的献祭
You'll have your sacrifice.
但在我死之前，我还有事要办
But I have things to do before I die.
你要我们卑躬屈膝地去参加
女巫的活动，还要献礼？
You want us to go to a witch event
on bended knee and give them a gift?
真抱歉，但我没记错的话
(SCOFFS) I'm sorry,
but I just remembered,
那晚我们正好已经有安排了
we're busy doing just about
anything else that night.
迪亚哥，这不是请求
Diego, this isn't a request.
协定上有你的名字
Your name is on that treaty.
如果你对你的新职位
Now, if you have
any difficulty whatsoever
有什么不适应的话
with your newfound position,
我很愿意把你换掉
I'd be more than willing
to remove you.
我还真没想到会有这一天
I never thought I'd see the day.
吸血鬼向女巫屈服
Vampires bowing down to witches.
我视它为一种实力的展现
I see it as a demonstration
of strength.
向弱小致敬
Acknowledging a lesser faction.
但你并不是在请求，对吧？
But you're not asking, are you?
看来他们关于你的言论是真的，以利亚
I see it's true what
they say about you, Elijah.
你会把暴力也伪装得很高尚
You make even
strong-arming seem noble.
不过…
Well....
游客们很吃这一套
The tourists do eat this stuff up.
你能想像当他们突然发现
Can you imagine what they'd think if
这一切都是真的会怎么想吗？
they suddenly found
out it was all real?
我想你是要我出席公开表演
I take it you want me
at the public show
和之后的私人聚会是吗？
and the private party afterward?
是的
That is correct.
我很乐意参加
I'd be happy to attend.
这样你就欠人类一个人情了
And in return, you will
owe the humans a favor.
你们族人能有如此气魄
Your people are uniquely poised
为法语区的其他族群树立榜样
to set an example for
the rest of the French Quarter.
这也就是为什么狼人参与
此次活动如此重要
Which is why it's important
for the wolves to attend.
心意领了，但我们不去
Thanks but no thanks?
先听他说完
Let's hear the man out.
那些女巫对你们狼群施了咒
The witches are the ones
that cursed your pack.
也是她们，自我一进城
And they've been
nothing but crap to me
就给我找麻烦，不去
since I first came to town. No.
我们不会去
We're not going.
此一时彼一时了，海莉
It's a new day
in the Quarter, Hayley.
我同意奥利佛的想法
I agree with Oliver.
只有相互配合，才能共存
If we're gonna coexist,
we have to play ball.
我们会派代表带着礼物前去
We'll send a representative
with a gift.
这未免太容易了
That was too easy.
不要相信他
Don't trust him.
不要相信他们任何人
Don't trust any of them.
别试图反抗了
You don't stop squirming,
我可不管你认识什么人
再动我就打碎你的膝盖
I don't care who you know,
I'm gonna kneecap you right here.
我是要你把凯瑞当作客人带来给我
When I asked you to bring Cary
to me, it was as my guest.
你最好放开他
Might I recommend you release him
不然我就送你上西天
before I opt to release you
from your mortal coil.
我照你的吩咐找到了他
然后他攻击了我
I found him like you
asked and he jumped me.
他的狼群一直在攻击我的狼群
Now, his pack's been going at mine
since the beginning of time.
我可什么都不欠他
I don't owe him a thing.
瞧，就是这样的短见
You see, it's that
shortsighted attitude
导致了狼人的垮台
that led to the demise
of the werewolves.
我确定这是马赛尔和女巫造成的
I'm pretty sure Marcel
and the witches did that.
狼群本该团结一心
The packs should have been united.
马赛尔发现了你们的弱点并利用它
Marcel saw that weakness
and he exploited it.
如果你们只想靠新月族重建狼族
If you seek to rebuild
with only the Crescents,
那你们就该待在沼泽的茅舍别出来
you may as well stay
in your hovels in the bog.
我想我还没有幸自我介绍一下
I don't believe we've had
the pleasure of an introduction.
传闻你是我族一脉的后裔
Legend says you're
descended from our line.
传闻是真的
The legends are true.
凯瑞，我知道这枚戒指是我们家族
Now, Cary, I understand that
this ring was passed down
世世代代传下来的
through generations of our family.
我想知道它放在哪个石头里
I need to know what stone it housed.
我从没见过什么石头
I never saw it with a stone.
能帮我打听一下吗，兄弟？
Could you ask around
for me, mate? Hmm?
看看能不能有所发现
See what you can find out.
你无法光靠自己就发动一场革命
DlEGO: You can't just start
a revolution all on your own
结束流放重掌大权
from exile across the river.
我是说，不管你喜不喜欢
以利亚的计划就是新的现实
I mean, like it or not, Elijah's
plan is the new reality.
以利亚要你对女巫卑躬屈膝
Elijah's got you
bowing down to witches.
过不了多就你就要对狼人俯首称臣了
How long until you're
kowtowing to werewolves?
好吧，那谁来领导这次谋反？你吗？
Right. And who's gonna lead
this rebellion? You?
我倒是有些想法
I got a few ideas.
我记得上次与你一起对抗真祖时的情形
I remember the last time I stood
with you against an Original.
过程并不顺利
Didn't go so well.
我们所要做的就是表明我们不会屈服
All we gotta do is show
that we won't bow down.
制造足够的泥乱，他们就会离开
Make enough noise, they'll leave.
我想如果我们团结起来，力量会更大
I figure we can be a lot louder
if we're in it together.
听着，以利亚米卡森无疑是个混蛋
Look, Elijah Mikaelson's
a dick, no doubt.
但和他在一起，我至少清楚自己的立场
Thing is, with him,
at least I know where I stand.
是吗？
Do you?
我们一直在监视克劳斯
We've been watching Klaus.
他和女巫做交易
与狼人秘密会面
Making deals with witches, holding
secret meetings with werewolves.
你不能相信这些人
You can't trust these people.
是你捡起了克劳斯的硬币
You're the one who
picked up Klaus's coin.
是你，马赛尔
小提也许记性不好，但我不是
You, Marcel. Maybe T's
got a short memory, but I don't.
你是个懦夫
You're a coward.
我捡起硬币的时候，是在为你们着想
When I picked up that coin,
I was saving your ass.
克劳斯要把你们全部杀掉
Klaus was gonna kill all of you.
一个好的领袖知道何时该放手择日再战
A good leader knows when
he's gotta fight another day.
现在这一天来了
我准备好了，你要与我并肩作战吗？
Now that day's here.
I'm ready. You gonna fight with me?
用什么战？
看看四周
With what? Look around.
你只有提艾里和一堆空话
All you got is Thierry
and a whole bunch of talk.
你们看来还没认清现实，你已经输了
You guys don't seem to get it.
You lost, all right?
我选择了赢的那一方
如果你想要开战
I picked the winning side,
so if you want to start a war...
你就是我的敌人
...you're fighting against me.
该以行动说话了
Time we got more persuasive.
怎么了？这是高中吗？
What is this?
High School?
你还是接受暗示管好你自己的事吧
Why don't you take the hint
and mind your own business?
这是我的族群
所以这就是我的事
This is my pack.
That makes it my business.
没必要动气，对你不好，海莉
No need to get all riled up.
It's not good for you, Hayley.
我刚刚已经试过好好说了
I have tried to play nice.
怀孕后期荷尔蒙和情绪波动比较大
The last month of pregnancy is
all hormones and mood swings,
除非你希望我把你的胳膊扭断
so unless you want me
to snap your arm like a twig,
不然你最好告诉我发生了什么事
I suggest that you
tell me what is going on.
- 你去死吧
- 别这样
-You can go to hell.
-Knock it off.
没理由瞒着她
There's no reason
to keep it from her.
我倒是有个理由
I can think of a reason.
高大永生，口袋还放手帕的人
Tall and immortal and wears
a pocket scarf.
海莉，你是我们的一员，你应该知道
Hayley, you're one of us.
You deserve to know.
有话好好说
Now, come on..
我们缔结了一个联盟
We made an alliance...
这对狼人将是个重大转折
...that's gonna change everything
for the wolves.
与谁结盟？
An alliance with who?
克劳斯
Klaus.
跟我详细说
Tell me everything.
你大老远跑来就是求我救一个人类？
You came all this way to
beg for some human's life?
基兰神父就快没时间了
他一直是我的盟友
Father Kieran's time is running out
and he has been an ally to me.
你的盟友，也是卡蜜的叔叔
Your ally, and Cami's uncle.
抱歉，就像我说过的
这个咒语没办法撤销
Sorry. As I've already said,
there's no way to undo that hex.
得了吧，我们都知道咒语总有漏洞
Oh, come on. You and I both
know there's always a loophole.
这个没有
Not for this.
至少我的族人没找到
At least not among my people.
不过我倒是很好奇
Although I do wonder.
你的母亲很强大
Your mother was powerful.
她会各种形式的咒语
She would have had access
to all manner of spells.
也许我可以看看她的魔法书
Perhaps I could take a look
through her grimoire.
你想用基兰神父的病痛当作借口
You want to use
Father Kieran's ailment
趁机翻看我母亲的魔法书
as an excuse to look through
my mother's spellbook.
真狡猾
Very devious.
得了吧，魔法书对你来说根本没用
Come on.
The grimoire is worthless to you.
但借助它的力量
我就能巩固我在族群的地位
But with its power, I could
solidify my place in the coven.
不行，抱歉，亲爱的
No, I'm sorry, love.
我母亲的力量被你的祖先神圣化
已经够糟了
It's bad enough my mother's power was
consecrated with your ancestors.
我绝对不会让你看到
The last thing I need is
for you to get a look
她那一整本龌龊的小伎俩
at an entire book
of her dirty, little tricks.
那真是太遗憾了
That's unfortunate.
尤其是对可怜的基兰神父来说
Particularly for poor Father Kieran.
我想还是由你来告诉卡蜜吧
I guess you'll be the one
to tell Cami.
你觉得你能掌控我吗？
You think you have leverage over me?
我不会被操纵的
I will not be manipulated.
我也不会被威胁，所以
And I won't be threatened.
So, between the two of us,
既然我们都清楚自己的立场
we each know where we stand.
只要我们能保持互相尊重
As long as we can retain
that mutual respect,
我看就没必要再展示各自的力量了吧
I don't see a need for any
further demonstrations of power.
别再打给我了
Don't call me again.
是时候了
It's time.
克劳斯会出席活动
也就是说宅邸没人
Klaus will be at the event, which
means the compound will be empty.
你知道该怎么做
You know what to do.
现在，根据恩典节的程序
Now, in accordance with
the Fete des Benedictions,
纽奥良的女巫们会赐福予你们所有人
the witches of New
Orleans bless you all.
有点太容易了，不是吗？
KLAUS: A little too easy, isn't it?
我正在等你
I've been expecting you.
你迟到了
You're late.
黛维娜
Davina.
以利亚
Elijah.
很高兴见到你
It's lovely to see you.
而且状况还蛮不错的
And under far better circumstances.
是吗？
Is it?
我朋友提姆还是死的
而你的弟弟还活着
My friend Tim is still dead and
your brother's still breathing.
黛维娜，够了
Davina, that's enough.
以利亚是今晚活动的赞助人
Elijah has been a patron
to us this evening.
我们应该对他尊重些
We will show him respect.
谢谢你所做的一切
Thank you for all of this.
这不是为了你
This isn't for you.
你我都清楚
如果我们不对你的族人表示些尊重
You know as well as I that your
people would never accept a truce
她们永远不会接受休战
unless we showed them some respect.
那就这样吧
So be it.
祝你派对愉快
Enjoy your party.
真奇怪，我以为你会
和你那些有趣的朋友在一起呢
Strange. I thought you'd be in the
company of your colorful friends.
你需要一个狼人代表
You asked for a representative
for the werewolves,
所以接不接受随你
so.... take me or leave me.
有什么问题吗？
Is something wrong?
这些人是来赞美女巫的
These people came to praise witches.
她做了什么证明了自己的价值？
What's she done
to prove herself worthy?
她是个收获祭女孩，和你一样
She's a Harvest girl.
Like you.
我们的力量是祖先的恩赐
Our power is a gift
from the ancestors.
为了这份恩赐我做出了牺牲
I've had to make sacrifices
to honor that gift.
我失去了我的母亲、阿姨
I lost my mother.
My aunt.
黛维娜除了跟我们作对什么都没做
Davina has done nothing
but stand against us.
她只是需要一些教训
She just needs a little lesson.
如果要说我擅长什么的话
那就是让人们安守本分
If there's one thing I'm good at,
it's putting people in their place.
欢迎
Welcome.
现在要进行我们历史悠久的传统
As is our time-honored tradition,
很欢迎各位送上你们的祭品
you are all welcome
to deliver your offerings.
我们的传统是任何人都不应被拒绝
It is our custom that no one
should be turned away,
任何祝福都不应被拒绝
no blessing be denied.
你收到礼物了吗？
Do you get any gifts?
你来这里干什么？
What are you doing here?
其实我是擅自进来的
但我是来见你的
Technically, I'm crashing,
but it's you I came to see.
别担心，我只想说完要说的话
然后我就会离开
Don't worry, I just want to say
my piece and then I'll leave.
给你
Here.
这是什么？
And what is this?
是我的祭品
An offering, from me.
我知道我们没理由喜欢彼此
I know we have no reason
to like each other,
但我想向以利亚建立的一切表示敬意
but I want to honor
what Elijah has built.
我叔叔也曾为此努力过
What my uncle worked for.
原来是为了你叔叔的事
Oh. So this is about your uncle.
如我所说，我知道你没理由帮我
Like I said, I know you have no
reason to help me,
但克劳斯说
很久以前，你被欺骗死去
but Klaus said a long time ago,
you were cheated out of life, and
如果我不能帮他，如果你不能帮他
他也帮不了他
if I can't help him, if you can't
help him, so will he.
所以我请求你，求求你
And so I'm asking you.... please.
克劳斯说你来自这个时代
Klaus said you were from this era.
- 我想你有头红发…
- 我曾经有一个和这个一样的
-And I thought with your red hair....
-I had one just like this.
也许我能帮你
Perhaps I can help you.
小约，你怎么来了？
Josh. What are you doing here?
你开玩笑吗？
我才不会错过你的重要日子
What, are you kidding?
No way I'd miss out on your big day.
再说了，音乐、微风、火焰
Besides, music, wind, fire....
内心那个爱玩的我彷佛置身天堂
The club kid in me
is, like, in heaven.
不过你看起来并不开心
You don't look like you're
having much fun, though.
来吧，我们离开这里
Come on. Let's get out of here.
约书亚
Joshua.
真是太巧了，能在这找到你
What a fortunate coincidence
finding you here.
我们还有事没了结呢
We have unfinished business.
你给我马上离开这里
You need to leave here right now.
平心而论，亲爱的
你已经不像以前那样强大了，不是吗？
To be fair, love, you're not quite as
powerful as you once were, are you?
你没资格下命今
You're in no position to give orders.
- 来吧，小伙子
- 我们能谈一下吗？
-(GROANlNG)
-Come along, lad.
OK, can we talk about this?
小约
Josh!
各位来宾，请注意
Ladies and gentlemen,
may I have your attention, please.
今天我们齐聚一堂
向我们爱戴的女巫们表示敬意
We are gathered here today to pay
homage to our beloved witches.
但有一位非常特别的女巫
But one very special witch
却完全被忽略了
has been utterly ignored.
在我看来有点不公平
That seems a little unfair to me.
不要
No.
我不想要你的礼物
I don't want your gift.
鉴于我们的过往
我了解你为什么拒绝我
I understand why you would
reject me, given our past.
事实上，今天在场有许多人
在我哥哥一纸协定所终结的冲突中
In truth, many of us here today
have been wronged in the conflict,
被冤枉了
which my brother's treaty ended.
你的朋友小约曾密谋杀我
Your friend Josh was involved
in a plot to kill me.
此时此刻，我本有权利
It would be well within my right
在此处决他
to execute him here and now.
但是，秉着团结一致的精神
But.... in the spirit of solidarity,
以及看在你的份上，黛维娜
我在此原谅他
and for your favor, Davina,
I hereby pardon him.
小约，从今往后，你再也不用害怕我
Josh.... from this day forward,
you have nothing to fear from me.
请收下
Please.
你要打开吗？
So are you gonna open it?
怎么了？是什么？
What? What is it?
这是制作日光戒指的咒语
It's the spell
that makes daylight rings.
我听说你让狼人们留下了深刻的印象
I hear you made quite an
impression with the wolves.
我与他们的安排本该是个秘密
My arrangement with them
was supposed to be a secret,
而你却逼他们说出来
and yet you forced it out of them.
真是大胆
It's very bold.
就像你今天决定代表他们独自来出席
As was your decision to represent
them here today, on your own.
我相信你绝不会做出危害我们目标的事
I trust you'll do nothing
to harm our cause.
你真的要背着以利亚吗？
Are you really gonna go
behind Elijah's back?
得了，只要对你的族人有利
Come on, what difference
does it make to you
这对你有何区别？
as long as your people benefit?
如果让我发现你在玩什么把戏
试图为了你的某个阴谋
If I find out that you are playing
some game, trying to manipulate us
- 而操纵我们…
- 你真是大有长进啊
-for one of your schemes--
-You know, you've come a long way...
小狼
...Iittle wolf.
我知道你很强悍，也知道你很精明
I knew you were tough,
I knew you were cunning,
但我从不知道你是女王
but I never knew you were a queen.
恩典节快乐
Happy Fete des Benedictions.
我们有消息要带给你们
We have a message
for all of you,
是马赛尔杰拉德的
from Marcel Gerard.
控制好自己
Control yourselves.
这是个下流的诡计
This is a vulgar trick.
我们不能违反协定
We do not violate our agreement.
海莉
Hayley!
带她们离开这里
Get them out of here!
- 以利亚？
- 海莉
-Elijah?
-Hayley.
没事
没事了
It's OK.
It's all right.
（永无宁日）
墙上的血迹、一堆尸体
THlERRY: Blood on the walls.
Pile of bodies.
总而尝之，消息大家都收到了
All in all, I'd say message received.
有没有先把黛维娜带出去？
Did you get Davina out first?
正如计划的一样，小约照顾黛维娜
As planned, Josh took care of Davina.
我确保其他收获祭女孩安全离开
I made sure the other Harvest
girls got out in the clear.
那只是个警告
That was just a warning shot.
现在我们要加倍了
Now we double down.
马赛尔！
-ELlJAH: Marcel!
-(THlERRY GRUNTlNG)
我警告过你了
I warned you.
但你还是回到了法语区
And yet still you return
to the French Quarter.
你要杀了我吗，以利亚？动手吧
You gonna kill me, Elijah? Go ahead.
但你就没法知道克劳斯和他的女巫
But then you won't know
what Klaus has got going
有何打算了
with that witch in his pocket.
我究竟该怎么做呢？
我想我可以直接问他
Whatever shall I do?
I suppose I could just ask him.
是啊，一定要让他告诉你
Yeah. Make sure
he tells you all about
他和狼人的那些秘密会面
the secret meetings
with the werewolves.
就是说，一旦他知道你杀了我
That is, if he's
still speaking to you
他还会告诉你吗？
once he knows that you killed me.
难道你不了解我吗？
Do you not know me?
你不听话的下场
For your violation.
不，不，不
No. No, no.
不
No.
你生，或死，都由我决定
You live.... or you die
according to my will.
努力记住吧
Try to remember that.
你没有拿我的祭品就离开了
You left without my offering.
你的吸血鬼毁了我的派对
Your vampires ruined my party.
他们不再是我的吸血鬼了，亲爱的
They're not my
vampires anymore, love.
尽管马赛尔显然是效仿了
我擅长的戏剧效果
Although Marcel certainly took a page
out of my book of dramatic effect.
听着，我欠黛维娜一些安慰
因为我杀了她的初恋
Look, I owed Davina some consolation
because I killed her first love.
我真的想弥补我做过的坏事
I do try to make up
for my wrongdoings.
至于我们先前的小小争执
As with our little quarrel earlier.
来，给你
So. Here.
我今晚早些时候选的
I picked it out earlier tonight.
你的一位朋友帮了我一下
A friend of yours gave me a hand.
哪位朋友？
And what friend was that?
打开吧，自己看
Well, open it.
See for yourself.
你真以为我会让我母亲的魔法书
就那样不受保护吗？
Did you really think I would leave
my mother's grimoire unprotected?
一个世纪前，我曾梦想着
认识你会是怎样
A century ago, I dreamed of what
it would be like to know you.
现在我很庆幸我之前不认识你
Now I'm glad I didn't.
我也许太天真才会爱上你，或害怕你
I might have been naive enough
to fall for you, or fear you,
但我从死亡中学到了很多
相信我，克劳斯米卡森
but I learned a lot in death
and trust me, Klaus Mikaelson,
你才应该害怕我
it's you who should be afraid of me.
真可惜，我会怀念和你上床的
Pity. I will miss the sex.
你的朋友卡蜜今晚来过
Your friend Cami showed up tonight.
她的祭品真的很不错
Her offering was quite sweet.
所以我给了她希望
说我会解除基兰的诅咒
So I gave her hope
that I would lift Kieran's hex,
但根本就没希望
but there is no hope.
或者曾经有，但现在没了
Or if there was, there isn't now.
如果神父死了，相信我
If the priest dies, then believe me,
你会迅速随他而去的
you will follow swiftly after him.
如果你要杀了我，一个潜在的盟友
It would be foolish of
you to kill me,
只为了一个软弱无力的人类
a potential ally,
那你真是太傻了
而她，顺便一提
in defense of some powerless
human who is, by the way,
还和你的敌人马赛尔上床了
sleeping with your enemy.... Marcel.
我学到教训了
I've learned my lesson.
一开始我反对你的计划
At first I was against your plan.
我以为我们能在以利亚的协定下生存
I thought that we should just
live with Elijah's treaty,
但在这派对之后，那些无辜的人
but after that party,
those innocent people.
绝不会有和平
There will never be a peace.
弱者永远只能任凭强者宰割
The weak will always be at the mercy
of whoever is calling the shots.
适者生存
It's survival of the fittest.
我们得保护自己
We need to protect ourselves.
我们必须保护彼此
And we.... we need
to protect each other.
趁克劳斯还愿意提供帮助
我们要加以利用
We need to use Klaus's help
while he's still willing to give it.
但杰克森
But Jackson....
从今往后，你不能对我有所隐瞒
From now on, you
have to tell me everything.
并且不管怎样
我们都不能相信克劳斯
And no matter what....
we do not trust Klaus.
看来你已经为小狼报仇了
Well, I see that you've already
avenged the little wolf.
但看你的表情，你还要继续杀人
But judging by your look,
you're still out for blood.
如果疯狂的定义就是反覆做同样的事情
If the definition of insanity is
doing the same thing repeatedly
还期待着不同的结局
and expecting different results,
那么无疑我对你的救赎的追求
then surely my quest
for your salvation
已让我成了最疯狂的人之一
ranks me as one
of the maddest of men.
说吧
这个私生子这次又干了什么可怕的事？
Come on, then. What horrible deed
has the bastard done this time?
你知道在过去，我确实很欣赏
Do you know, in the past,
I actually appreciated
你操纵一切的手段
the methods to your manipulations.
然而，我们现在
处在一个新时代的边缘
However, now here we are,
poised on the brink of a new era
不仅有利于你的家，还有利于你的孩子
which will benefit not only
your home but your child,
而你却背着我跟狼人勾结
and you go behind my back
to conspire with wolves.
家庭会议用不上勾结这个词吧
Conspire is hardly the word
I would use for a family council.
你不要忘了，以利亚，他们是我的家人
Lest you forget, Elijah,
they are my family
和任何米卡森家的人一样
as much as any Mikaelson,
而这名字，实际上，都不能算是我的姓
a name, in truth,
I cannot even call my own.
你怎么能随意就否认了
你姓了一千年的姓
How casually you disavow 1,000
years of allegiance towards you.
既然我找到了我的其他家人
And now that I've found the remnants
我难道要无视他们的困境吗？
of my other family,
am I to ignore their plight?
我本以为你会支持我
想要帮助他们的愿望
I would've thought you'd
support my desire to help them,
这样做，我也算帮了海莉和孩子
when in doing so,
I help Hayley, and the child.
不要质疑我对孩子的真心
Do not question my allegiance
towards that child.
那我想你对海莉的感情
Oh, and I suppose
your affection for Hayley
和你不知疲倦的奉献毫无关系
has nothing to do with
your tireless dedication.
是的，我今晚看到你对她的关心
Yes, you see, I saw how
you cared for her tonight.
黑暗中呼唤着她的名字
Called her name in the dark.
特别热衷杀死所有会伤害她的人
The zeal with which you destroy
those who would harm her.
我克制住每一次对那个女人的冲动
I have denied every single impulse
I have ever had for that woman.
是出于对你的尊敬
Out of some misbegotten respect
而你根本不在乎
for intentions that
you don't even have.
- 我警告你…
- 我警告你
-I'm warning you--
-I'm warning you.
我原谅了你，我站在你这边
I've forgiven you.
I have stood by you.
我抛弃了一切欲望
I've forsaken every single
one of my desires
只为了你的可笑的救赎
in the name of your
ridiculous redemption.
再也不会了
如果我想要什么
No more.
If I want something...
我就会得到它
...I'll take it.
没有什么，什么都不会阻碍我
And nothing.... nothing....
will stand in my way.
- 克劳斯，你…
- 我是来道歉的
-Klaus, what are you--
-I came here to apologize.
我犯了一个严重的错误
I've made a terrible mistake.
不管是什么，你该睡一觉把它忘记
Whatever it is,
you should sleep it off.
我确定可以等到明天早上再说
I'm sure it can wait till morning.
你去找了洁妮薇
You went to Genevieve.
她被你的恳求打动了
She was moved by your plea.
她甚至可能治好基兰
She may even have cured Kieran.
但我侮辱了她
But I insulted her.
作为报复的一种手段
她拒绝帮助他
And as a means of revenge,
she is refusing him aid.
基兰会因我而死
Kieran will die because of me.
而且会死得很惨
And it will be a horrible death.
你为什么要告诉我？
Why are you telling me this?
因为我相信秘密就是毒药
Because I believe that
secrets are a poison.
需要吐出来
They need to be spat out.
就像你的秘密
Like your secret...
你和马赛尔在一起的秘密
...about your time with Marcel.
这不正是你想要的吗？
Isn't that what you wanted?
你魅惑我与马赛尔约会
You compelled me
to go out with Marcel.
你让我做你的间谋
You made me your spy.
也许我们在一起是你的错
And maybe it's your fault
we got together,
你生气是因为你没能控制住
and you're just mad because
you didn't get to control it.
你告诉马赛尔，如果再让我见到他
You tell Marcel if I see him again...
我会杀了他
...I'll kill him.
你不用一直来
You don't need to keep coming out.
如果出问题，我会告诉你的
I'd tell you if something was wrong.
她现在很好
But she's doing ok.
这女孩有着领导的天赋
The girl has a natural gift
for leading.
她让所有人都很惊讶
She surprised everyone.
不是所有人
Not everyone.
你想加入我们吗？
Do you want to.... join us?
我想要的…
What I want...
只是那女孩能快乐
...is for that girl to be happy.
别告诉她我来过
Don't tell her I was here.
这是提艾里范舒
MARCEL" This is Thierry Vanchure,
出色的小号手
mean-ass horn player,
勇敢女人的恋人
Iover of feisty women,
女巫、吸血鬼，还有人类
witch, vampire, and human alike.
我和他一起重建了这座城市
他一直支持着我
I rebuilt this city with him
and he always had my back.
即使我搞砸了，忘记了
Even when I screwed up
and forgot to have his.
而现在…
And now...
我只能向你保证，小提
...all I can do
is promise you this, T.
我不会让你白白牺牲
I won't let you die in vain.
我会夺回我们的城市
I will take back our city.
即使我得先将它烧成灰烬
Even if I have to burn it down first.
要继续对抗真祖吗？
Going up against The Originals?
真的，绝不放弃吗？
For real, no backing down?
绝不放弃
No backing down.
你让我们失望了
You failed us.
我说过，这需要时间
I told you. It will take time.
你觉得祖先会在乎你的借口吗？
Do you think the ancestors
care about your excuses?
吸血鬼攻击了我们
我们没有获得全部力量前
The vampires attacked us.
We can't retaliate
根本无法报复
until we possess our full strength.
你的献祭是最后一步
Your sacrifice is the final step.
他们说什么？
-What are they saying?
-(PANTlNG)
他们说让你活着
They told me to let you live.
但他们想要其他祭品作为交换
But in exchange,
they want another offering.
他们选中的人
One of their choosing.
告诉我，不管他们想要什么
我都会保证献给他们
Tell me. Whatever it is they want,
I will make sure they get it.
我发誓
I swear it.
是那个孩子
It's the child.
他们要我们杀了克劳斯的孩子
They want us to kill Klaus's child.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）